<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MyRecipeApp</string>
    <string name="main_title">My Recipe App</string>
    <string name="title1">Spaghetti bolognese</string>
    <string name="time1">60m to cook</string>
    <string name="desc1">Heat oil in a large saucepan over medium-high heat.
        Cook onion, carrot, celery and garlic, stirring, for 5 minutes
        or until softened. Add mince. Cook, breaking up with a wooden spoon,
        for 6 to 8 minutes or until browned. Add paste, tomatoes, oregano,
        nutmeg, sweetener and 1/2 cup cold water. Bring to the boil.
        Reduce heat to low. Simmer, uncovered, for 20 to 30 minutes or
        until thick. Season with salt and pepper. Meanwhile, cook pasta in a
        large saucepan of boiling, salted water, following packet directions,
        until tender. Drain. Divide pasta among serving bowls. Spoon over sauce.
        Serve topped with cheese and fresh basil.
    </string>
    <string name="link1">https://img.taste.com.au/jWj_REwj/w720-h480-cfill-q80/taste/2016/11/spaghetti-bolognese-118369-2.jpg</string>

    <string name="title2">Zucchini fritters</string>
    <string name="time2">30m to cook</string>
    <string name="desc2">Trim the ends from zucchini. Coarsely grate the zucchini.
        Place in a colander and squeeze out as much excess moisture as possible.
        Transfer to a bowl. Stir in self-raising flour, parmesan, shallots, egg,
        parsley, oregano, salt and nutmeg. Heat 1 teaspoon olive oil in a non-stick frying
        pan over medium-high heat. Drop three portions of zucchini mixture into pan.
        Cook for 1 1/2 minutes each side or until golden and cooked through.
        Transfer to a plate. Repeat with remaining olive oil and remaining zucchini mixture.
</string>
    <string name="link2">https://img.taste.com.au/g5UZaMfb/w720-h480-cfill-q80/taste/2016/11/zucchini-fritters-76488-1.jpeg</string>

    <string name="title3">Minestrone soup</string>
    <string name="time3">65m to cook</string>
    <string name="desc3">Place the bacon, carrots, celery and potato in a large saucepan and stir
        to combine. Cook over high heat, uncovered, stirring often, for 5 minutes. Add the garlic,
        beef stock, tomatoes and red kidney beans to the pan, cover and bring to the boil. Reduce
        heat to medium-low. Simmer, covered, stirring occasionally, for 30 minutes or until the
        vegetables are tender. Increase heat to high. Add pasta and cook, uncovered, stirring
        occasionally, following packet directions or until pasta is al dente. Season with salt and
        pepper. Ladle into serving bowls and sprinkle with parsley. Serve immediately.
    </string>
    <string name="link3">https://img.taste.com.au/Lpk9jakR/w720-h480-cfill-q80/taste/2010/01/minestrone_soup_1980x1320-117900-1.jpg</string>

    <string name="title4">Curried sausages</string>
    <string name="time4">60m to cook</string>
    <string name="desc4">Heat oil in a large, heavy-based saucepan over medium-high heat. Cook
        sausages, in batches, turning, for 5 to 6 minutes or until browned all over. Transfer to
        a large plate. Add onion, carrot and garlic. Cook, stirring, for 5 minutes or until onion
        has softened. Add curry powder. Cook, stirring, for 30 seconds or until fragrant.
        Add fruit chutney and stock. Return sausages to pan. Cover, bring to the boil.
        Reduce heat to medium-low. Simmer, uncovered, for 25 minutes or until sausages are
        cooked through and sauce thickens. Stir in peas. Season. Cook for 1 to 2 minutes or until
        heated through. Serve with steamed rice and sprinkled with parsley leaves.</string>
    <string name="link4">https://img.taste.com.au/cQSEA7BY/w720-h480-cfill-q80/taste/2016/11/curried-sausages-72753-1.jpeg</string>

    <string name="title5">Pumpkin soup</string>
    <string name="time5">50m to cook</string>
    <string name="desc5">Heat oil in a large saucepan over low heat, add onion and leek and cook
        for 2-3 minutes, until softened but not coloured. Add garlic and spices and cook, stirring,
        for 30 seconds. Add pumpkin, potato and stock and bring to the boil. Turn heat to low,
        cover and simmer for 30 minutes. Allow to cool slightly, then blend in batches. Return soup
        to pan, stir through cream and reheat gently. Season and add a little more nutmeg if desired.</string>
    <string name="link5">https://img.taste.com.au/lNSYKI_b/w720-h480-cfill-q80/taste/2010/01/best-easy-pumpkin-soup-recipe-185570-1.jpg</string>

</resources>